<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scriptic</title>
    <link>https://www.scriptic.co.nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Scriptic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.scriptic.co.nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplified Server-side Paging, Sorting, and Filtering with Angular-DataTables and .NET</title>
      <link>https://www.scriptic.co.nz/blog/2016/12/simplified-server-side-paging-sorting-and-filtering-with-angular-datatables-and-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scriptic.co.nz/blog/2016/12/simplified-server-side-paging-sorting-and-filtering-with-angular-datatables-and-net/</guid>
      <description>Introduction. It would be fair to say that I&amp;rsquo;m not a UX designer. I try (sometimes harder than I should) to make things look pretty, but I generally go for a minimalist style in my projects (the Hugo theme used for this blog is a good example), if only to reduce the number of hours I would otherwise waste lining my pixels up just right. As a result, I tend to overuse html tables as a medium for information display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing a .NET Core Console Application as an Azure Web Job from Visual Studio</title>
      <link>https://www.scriptic.co.nz/blog/2016/11/publishing-a-net-core-console-application-as-an-azure-web-job-from-visual-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scriptic.co.nz/blog/2016/11/publishing-a-net-core-console-application-as-an-azure-web-job-from-visual-studio/</guid>
      <description>Introduction. Azure web Jobs are super useful for long-running or low priority tasks that need to be run in the background of a web application. They are a light weight alternative to worker roles or virtual machines.
With the knowledge that it is a supported scenario, I decided to experiment with using a .NET Core console application. I had absolutely no problems getting the application to run as a Web Job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Python Tools for Visual Studio to debug a Google App Engine project</title>
      <link>https://www.scriptic.co.nz/blog/2016/10/using-python-tools-for-visual-studio-to-debug-a-google-app-engine-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.scriptic.co.nz/blog/2016/10/using-python-tools-for-visual-studio-to-debug-a-google-app-engine-project/</guid>
      <description>General Setup. First we need to install the following packages
 Python Tools for Visual Studio which is now included in the list of features when running setup. Python 2.7 Google App Engine SDK for Python  Next, create a Python project, create a virtual environment, and install the ptvsd python package.
Right click the project file -&amp;gt; Properties, and make the following changes.
General
 Startup File: C:\Program Files (x86)\Google\google_appengine\dev_appserver.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>